[{"answer": "You just said everyone needs something", "docId": "Family-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Wow.  It must be great being you.  You got it all", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Thank you, my friend.  I know if I can just sleep this off, Ill be fine..", "docId": "Family-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "A shelter?!  Im the richest guy in the building...Ive got twice the square footage you have", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Why not", "docId": "Family-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Figure it out?  Figure what out?", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Where do I go now", "docId": "Family-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Big Eds?  Big Eds Tires?  Why...", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "No, I love my friend.  We had a lot of good times, didnt we", "docId": "Family-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "my friend?  In the Village?  When we were living in that place...?  Great times.  Whyd we ever leave", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Our life in a nutshell..", "docId": "Family-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "How would you look at it", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Something like that", "docId": "Family-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Youre a nurse", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What...", "docId": "Family-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Yeah, baby, I know what you like to hear..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I never used to be like this, my friend.  I had it all figured out.  No doubts, no regrets", "docId": "Family-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Now...I dont..", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Thats a big one for me, too", "docId": "Family-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Your pay check is a disgrace to pay checks", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I dont know how you did it, hoss, but you pulled it off", "docId": "Family-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Way out..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Mind if I ask what kind of sales you did last year? Ballpark..", "docId": "Family-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Uh huh...one point seven. And what do you project for this year", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Are you out of your mind", "docId": "Family-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend goes to a great school", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Its been interesting, thats for sure", "docId": "Family-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Youve been my friend.  And thats always a good thing..", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yes...my friend..", "docId": "Family-Man_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Yes, thats it...yes, we went to high school together", "qsentId": 30}]